Daniel Guevara

Montreal,QC 4850 Chemin de la côte des neiges https://danielgituser.github.io/cv.github.io/ dgv1616@gmail.com

Profile:

I bring expertise across a spectrum of industries, encompassing marketing, education, construction, architecture, interactive technology, and natural gas energy. I have been in charge of creating and overseeing the production of a wide range of digital assets. This includes web pages, web applications, web components, REST APIs, and database systems for software applications. Furthermore, I am well-versed in crafting TDD-tested code, ensuring robust and reliable solutions throughout the development process.

Experience:

Full Stack Web Developer / Back-End

IVN Labs 03/2020 - present

Plan, create, execute, and integrate front-end and back-end components into web applications

- · Database management (create, read, write, update and delete information from Databases, tables and field)
- Creation, modification and deletion of IT web applications, Models, Controllers, Views and databases
- · Create Test driven development files to ensure the correct implementation of code in the developments
- · Integration of APIs

Full Stack Web Developer / Back-End

IVN Studios 06/2016 - 02/2020

Full stack Web developer creating the front-end and back-end of apps

- · Database management (create, read, write, update and delete information from Databases, tables and field)
- · Creation, modification and deletion of IT web applications, Models, Controllers, Views, databases, etc
- Web Design Experience
- · Server management

Full Stack Web Developer

University Manuela Beltran

02/2014 - 03/2016

Full stack Web developer creating the front-end and back-end of educational web applications.

- · Make web design, hypermedia and web products, Create E-Material in HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP
- Managing Rest APIs databases connected to educational software
- Create content for virtual education Saas. Educational Remote experience of learning

Front End developer

Natual Gas Energy

01/2013 - 12/2013

Handle request and responses throw $\ensuremath{\mathsf{HTML}}$ and $\ensuremath{\mathsf{JSON}}$

· Handle response from controllers to front-end app views displaying the content to the corresponding HTML tags

Work by contract

Front-End Developer - Graphic Designer

04/2007 - 06/2013

· As freelance I work for clients as designer and as front end developer, creating their projects as requested

Programmer technical skills: Blade (HTML), Tailwind (CSS), JSON REST APIs, Laravel Framework, C#, Javascript, PHP Language, TDD Test Driven Development, OOP Object-oriented programming, Perforce P4V, Git, GitHub

Code Showcase Link

Designer technical skills: Adobe's Creative Apps suit, 3D Max modeler, Interactive Media, Real-Time Render Engines, Responsive Design, Typography studies, User Interfaces, User Experience, 3D Resin Printing, and molds maker.

Education & Certificates:

LCI LaSalle College International

Technologist in Computer Graphics, Animation, Multimedia and Web Apps Development.

03/2009 - 06/2012

WES Certification, Badge report Canadian equivalency: Diploma (three years)

WES Certifications

Institute PDC

PHP Web Applications Development Certificate

Laracasts Active since 2019

Web App Education

Concordia Univeristy of Montreal

Creative Thinking, Decision-making, Problem-solving, Information, Client Focus

Concordia - Certifications

Harvard University Currently Coursing

Major CS50's Computer Science

Skills:

· Spanish - Native | English - Advanced | French - Basic

CELPIP - Certification

- Leadership and teamwork, the ability to manage and delegate to others and take on responsibility on the tasks
- Detail oriented, well organized and continuously praised for outstanding performance.
- · Communication, Social person with ideas to share and learn from others
- · Driven by results and success. Reliable and dependable
- · Commercial awareness Organisational Awareness
- · Experience working with Startups

Daniel Guevara

Technician in Computer Graphics and Web App Development